Guide to the Erroll Garner Archive, 1942-2010 AIS.2015.09 AIS.2015.09
ULS Archives & Special Collections
- Photographs, V.
  - Black and White Candids, Studio, 2.
    - Garner and George Avakian, 2 photographs (Box 42, Folder 11)
      Photos of Erroll Garner with Columbia Records executive George Avakian.
    - Garner - Haze Cleveland, 1 photograph (Box 42, Folder 12)
      Portrait of Erroll Garner with Norwegian recording artist Haze Cleveland.
    - Paris, 1965; 4 photographs (Box 42, Folder 13)
      Photos of Erroll Garner arriving in Paris.
    - Paris trip photos, 1965; 11 photographs (Box 42, Folder 14)
    - Garner with towel, 1 photograph (Box 42, Folder 15)
    - B&W Candid, 123 photographs (Box 42, Folder 16)
      Assorted photos and portraits of Erroll Garner including performances, receiving awards, meeting with the mayor of Boston, travel, and with French jazz violinist, Stephane Grappelli.
    - B&W Candid, 117 photographs (Box 42, Folder 17)
      Assorted photos and portaits of Erroll Garner including performances, receiving awards, and travel.
    - B&W Studio, 135 photographs (Box 42, Folder 18)
      Assorted photos of Erroll Garner in the recording studio.
    - B&W Studio: New Kind of Love, Summer 1963; 55 photographs (Box 42, Folder 19)
      Photos from the "New Kind of Love" recording session.
    - B&W Studio, 78 photographs (Box 42, Folder 20)
    - B&W Studio, 41 photographs (Box 42, Folder 21)
    - B&W Studio: Columbia date Caravan album, 6 photographs (Box 42, Folder 22)
    - B&W Studio, 22 photographs (Box 42, Folder 23)
    - Candid, Matted prints, 5 photographs (Box 42, Folder 24)
      Souvenir matted photos from: Cafe Zanzibar, NYC; Zardi's Jassland, Hollywood; Frolic's, Salisbury Beach, Mass.; Three Deuces, NYC.
    - Photos mounted on board (portrait of Garner), 2 photographs (Box 42, Folder 25-26)
  - Black and White Publicity Images, 1950s-1970s; 3.
    - Publicity B&W, 67 photographs (Box 43, Folder 1)
      Erroll Garner "Magician" album cover, assorted photos of Erroll Garner performing, in the recording studio, or with others.
    - Publicity B&W, 3 photographs (Box 43, Folder 2)
    - Publicity B&W, 9 photographs (Box 43, Folder 3)
    - Publicity B&W, 41 photographs (Box 43, Folder 4)
    - Publicity B&W, 34 photographs (Box 43, Folder 5)
    - Publicity B&W, 28 photographs (Box 43, Folder 6)
      Assorted portraits of Erroll Garner, including some from his 1965 foreign tour.
    - Publicity B&W, 17 photographs (Box 43, Folder 7)
      Assorted portraits of Erroll Garner, along with photos of "Magician" album cover.
    - Publicity B&W, 28 photographs (Box 43, Folder 8)
    - Publicity B&W, 9 photographs (Box 43, Folder 9)
    - Publicity B&W, 3 photographs (Box 43, Folder 10)
    - Publicity B&W, 5 photographs (Box 43, Folder 11)
      Erroll Garner on the television show, "Dottie Hansen's Hi-Time," at the piano holding the key to the City of Pittsburgh, and assorted other portraits.
    - Publicity B&W, 5 photographs (Box 43, Folder 12)
    - Publicity B&W, 30 photographs (Box 43, Folder 13)
    - Publicity B&W, 2 photographs (Box 43, Folder 14)
    - Publicity B&W, 3 photographs (Box 43, Folder 15)
    - Publicity B&W, 18 photographs (Box 43, Folder 16)
    - London Sweater, 5 photographs (Box 43, Folder 17-18)
    - "London Sweater 'do not use'", 2 photographs (Box 43, Folder 19)
    - Baldwin Piano, 10 photographs (Box 44, Folder 1)
      Erroll Garner touring the Baldwin Piano factory in Cincinnati, Ohio.
    - [Merv]Griffin Show Headshot, 1967; 7 photographs (Box 44, Folder 2-5)
    - [Merv] Griffin Show, National Observer, 1967; 4 photographs (Box 44, Folder 6)
    - [Merv]Griffin- Garner, 1967; 22 photographs (Box 44, Folder 7)
    - Erroll Garner- Harpsicord, 3 items (Box 44, Folder 8)
    - Suit, piano, big smile, 7 photographs (Box 44, Folder 9)
    - "Magician" Cover, 20 photographs (Box 44, Folder 10)
    - Front of handbill, 5 photographs (Box 44, Folder 11)
    - [B&W] Publicity, 67 photographs (Box 44, Folder 12)
      Assorted portraits of Erroll Garner performing as well as other candid shots. Also includes Erroll Garner in the recording studio with composer Leith Stevens, a CD cover (1997), and Erroll Garner photo postcards.
    - "Up" cover, 9 photographs (Box 44, Folder 13)
    - "Up" cover (multiple copies), 22 photographs (Box 44, Folder 14)
    - [Merv] Griffin Show, 1967; 5 photographs (Box 44, Folder 15-16)
    - Kick Cover, 2 photographs (Box 44, Folder 17)
    - Mercury #4, 1 photographs (Box 44, Folder 18)
    - #1 Mercury "Spots On It!", 2 photographs (Box 44, Folder 19)
    - Back of Handbill, 23 photographs (Box 44, Folder 20)
    - Just Jazz PBS, 20 photographs (Box 44, Folder 21)
      Photos and performer posters from the PBS series "Just Jazz" for the following artists: Dexter Gordon, Ray Nance, Art Hodes, Don Byas, Bobby Hackett, Gene Ammons, Sounds of Swing, James Moody, and Erroll Garner.
  - Non-Matted Black and White Candid Images, 4.
    - Non-Matted B&W Candid, 78 photographs (Box 45, Folder 1)
    - Non-Matted B&W Candid, 16 photographs (Box 45, Folder 2)
    - Non-Matted B&W Candid, 93 photographs (Box 45, Folder 3)
    - Non-Matted B&W Candid, 72 photographs (Box 45, Folder 4)
    - Non-Matted B&W Candid, 35 photographs (Box 45, Folder 5)
    - Non-Matted B&W Candid, 56 photographs (Box 45, Folder 6)
    - Non-Matted B&W Candid, 23 photographs (Box 45, Folder 7)
    - Non-Matted B&W Candid, 11 photographs (Box 45, Folder 8)
    - Garner; Wilmington, 1965; 37 photographs (Box 45, Folder 9)
    - Garner Shoulder Shot, 2 photographs (Box 45, Folder 10)
    - Non-Matted B&W Candid (Box 45, Folder 11)
  - Black and White by Photographer, 5.
    - Aram Avakian, 8 photographs (Box 46, Folder 1)
    - Adrian of Boston, 2 photographs (Box 46, Folder 2)
    - Albert Fisher, 18 photographs (Box 46, Folder 3)
    - An Anderson Creation, 4 photographs (Box 46, Folder 4)
    - Andre Richard, 2 photographs (Box 46, Folder 5)
    - Arnold C. Demille, 2 photographs (Box 46, Folder 6)
    - Arthur Goldwyn, 5 photographs (Box 46, Folder 7)
    - A.S.L. (Actualites Suisses Lausanne), 11 photographs (Box 46, Folder 8)
    - Aviation News, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 9)
    - Bakalar-Cosmo Photographies, 4 photographs (Box 46, Folder 10)
    - Bengt H. Malmquist, 3 photographs (Box 46, Folder 11)
    - Bertrand Miles, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 12)
    - Blanc, 8 photographs (Box 46, Folder 13)
    - Bob Green, 8 photographs (Box 46, Folder 14)
    - Bettye Lane, 6 photographs (Box 46, Folder 15)
    - Bill Patton, 6 photographs (Box 46, Folder 16)
    - Brening, 28 photographs (Box 46, Folder 17)
    - Bruce Morissey, 4 photographs (Box 46, Folder 18)
    - Bruno Hollywood, 43 photographs (Box 46, Folder 19)
    - Cal-Pictures, 5 photographs (Box 46, Folder 20)
    - Cain Photo Service, 3 photographs (Box 46, Folder 21)
    - Camera Associates, Inc., 5 photographs (Box 46, Folder 22)
    - CBS, 7 photographs (Box 46, Folder 23)
    - Charles Steele, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 24)
    - Charles Stewart, 82 photographs (Box 46, Folder 25)
    - Charles "Teenie" Harris, 2 photographs (Box 46, Folder 26)
    - Chester Higgins Jr., 7 photographs (Box 46, Folder 27)
    - Columbia, 56 items (Box 46, Folder 28)
      Assorted photos of Erroll Garner from Columbia Records and a photo book from the WAJC Indianapolis 27 Hour Jazz Festival.
    - Combi Press Service, 34 photographs (Box 46, Folder 29)
    - Contienne Photographie, 3 photographs (Box 46, Folder 30)
    - David Workman, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 31)
    - Cristof Studio, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 32)
    - Dennis A. Stock, 5 photographs (Box 46, Folder 33)
    - Dorothy Siegel, 16 photographs (Box 46, Folder 34)
    - Doug McKenzie, 15 photographs (Box 46, Folder 35)
    - E. Hoffman, 4 photographs (Box 46, Folder 36)
    - Ebony Magazine (Mike Shea, Peter Hastings), 2 photographs (Box 46, Folder 37)
      - Mike Shea (Ebony Magazine), 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 37A)
        Photograph taken by Mike Shea for Ebony Magazine.
      - Peter Hastings (Ebony Magazine), 3 photographs (Box 46, Folder 37B)
        Photographs taken by Peter Hastings for Ebony Magazine.
    - Eiffert Studio, 6 photographs (Box 46, Folder 38)
    - Fay Foto Service, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 39)
    - Frank Wolfe (Box 46, Folder 40)
    - Franz Hemelrijk, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 41)
    - Fred Lyon, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 42)
    - Fred A. Sabine, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 43)
    - Fidelis Photos, 4 photographs (Box 46, Folder 44)
    - Fisher, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 45)
    - Gavin Davies, 2 photographs (Box 46, Folder 46)
    - Gene Gilbert, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 47)
    - Gene Howard, 2 photographs (Box 46, Folder 48)
    - Gene Price, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 49)
    - Guild Photographers, 20 photographs (Box 46, Folder 50)
    - Guy Le Querrec, 4 photographs (Box 46, Folder 51)
    - Hans Harzheim, 3 photographs (Box 46, Folder 52)
    - Henri Guilbaud, 2 photographs (Box 46, Folder 53)
    - Herman Leonard, 6 photographs (Box 46, Folder 54)
    - Harry Edelman, 2 photographs (Box 46, Folder 55)
    - J. Peter Happel, 2 photographs (Box 46, Folder 56)
    - Jaap Krant, 6 photographs (Box 46, Folder 57)
    - Jack Bradley, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 58)
    - Jack Foster, 2 photographs (Box 46, Folder 59)
    - Jack Tracy, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 60)
    - Jac Ten Broek, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 61)
    - Jacques Aubert-Philips, 9 photographs (Box 46, Folder 62)
    - James Bosch, 9 photographs (Box 46, Folder 63)
    - James J. Kreigsman (AKA JJK Copy Art), 2 photographs (Box 46, Folder 64)
    - Jan van Diepenbeek, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 65)
    - John Pierre Leloir, 48 photographs (Box 46, Folder 66)
    - Jean Planterose, 2 photographs (Box 46, Folder 67)
    - Jerry Campbell, 4 photographs (Box 46, Folder 68)
    - JJK Copy Art, 4 photographs (Box 46, Folder 69)
    - Joe Weisberg, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 70)
    - John Bos, 5 photographs (Box 46, Folder 71)
    - J.Y. McFerran, 3 photographs (Box 46, Folder 72)
    - Ken Palmer, 11 photographs (Box 46, Folder 73)
    - Keystone, 10 photographs (Box 46, Folder 74)
    - Klaus Guretzki, 3 photographs (Box 46, Folder 75)
    - Kovach Peter, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 76)
    - Lenscraft Photos, Inc., 2 photographs (Box 46, Folder 77)
    - Lili Eijsten, 30 photographs (Box 46, Folder 78)
    - Lois Miruiss Johnson, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 79)
    - Ludwig Binder, 13 photographs (Box 46, Folder 80)
    - Malcolm Poindexter, 3 photographs (Box 46, Folder 81)
    - Martin Cohen, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 82)
    - Matthews' News and Photo Agency (London), 4 photographs (Box 46, Folder 83)
    - Maynard Frank Wolfe – From Black Star, 4 photographs (Box 46, Folder 84)
    - Mayden Vienna, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 85)
    - M.J. Sleet Jr., 2 photographs (Box 46, Folder 86)
    - M.J. (Slim) Bent, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 87)
    - Morris Berman, 2 photographs (Box 46, Folder 88)
    - Mort Schreiber, 16 photographs (Box 46, Folder 89)
    - Music Workshop, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 90)
    - Orie Damewood, 2 photographs (Box 46, Folder 91)
    - Our World Foto, 2 photographs (Box 46, Folder 92)
    - Patricia Willard, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 93)
    - Patrick Bertrand, 4 photographs (Box 46, Folder 94)
    - Peter Perri, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 95)
    - Peter W. Dickenson, 1 photographs (Box 46, Folder 96)
    - (AB) Philips-Sonora, 7 photographs (Box 46, Folder 97)
    - Phillips Photographic Industries, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 98)
    - Photo Associates, 39 photographs (Box 46, Folder 99)
    - Photowetter (Germany), 8 photographs (Box 46, Folder 100)
    - Photopress, 21 photographs (Box 46, Folder 101)
    - Popsie, 53 items (Box 46, Folder 102)
      Photographs of Erroll Garner taken by the photographer William "Popsie" Randolph, as well as a booklet about Popsie's works, published in 2007.
    - Ray Whitten, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 103)
    - Raymond Ross, 2 photographs (Box 46, Folder 104)
    - Rebman, 8 photographs (Box 46, Folder 105)
    - Richard Schor (Celebrities included?), 11 photographs (Box 46, Folder 106)
    - Ringier Bilderdienst AG, 23 photographs (Box 46, Folder 107)
    - Roberto Polillo, 8 photographs (Box 46, Folder 108)
    - Sam Falls, 2 photographs (Box 46, Folder 109)
    - Slade, 2 photographs (Box 46, Folder 110)
    - T. Arihara, 3 photographs (Box 46, Folder 111)
    - Ted Howard, 3 photographs (Box 46, Folder 112)
    - Ted Kosinski, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 113)
    - Ted Williams, 2 photographs (Box 46, Folder 114)
    - Foto Roncaglia (Italian photographers?), 31 photographs (Box 46, Folder 115)
    - TWA Airlines, 6 photographs (Box 46, Folder 116)
    - United Photographers, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 117)
    - United Press International, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 118)
    - U.S. Army, 13 photographs (Box 46, Folder 119)
    - Van News Photo, Inc., 1 photographs (Box 46, Folder 120)
    - Vancouver Sun Photo, 2 photographs (Box 46, Folder 121)
    - Vernon Smith, 2 photographs (Box 46, Folder 122)
    - Veryl Oakland, 8 photographs (Box 46, Folder 123)
    - Vic Kelley, 44 photographs (Box 46, Folder 124)
    - Wallace – Zorn, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 125)
    - Walter Perkins, 6 photographs (Box 46, Folder 126)
    - Wells – Fagliano, 2 photographs (Box 46, Folder 127)
    - Willie Feagin, 2 photographs (Box 46, Folder 128)
    - Willoughby Gullachsen, 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 129)
    - Wilson Millan, 6 photographs (Box 46, Folder 130)
    - Yuzo Sato – The Swing Journal Co., LTD. (Japan), 1 photograph (Box 46, Folder 131)
  - Garner with Celebrities, Touring & Autographed, 6.
    - [Erroll] Garner & [Clint] Eastwood, 22 photographs (Box 47, Folder 1)
      Photographs of Erroll Garner meeting with Clint Eastwood to review a special edition of Garner's hit song "Misty" that was recorded for the 1971 Eastwood film, "Play Misty for Me."
    - With Celebrities, 294 photographs (Box 47, Folder 2-6)
    - Movie stills, 12 photographs (Box 47, Folder 7)
    - MGM Prints, 103 photographs (Box 47, Folder 8-11)
    - Feeling Cover, 1 photograph (Box 47, Folder 12)
    - Concert with Audience, 2 photographs (Box 47, Folder 13)
    - Swiss photo, 1966; 12 photographs (Box 47, Folder 14)
    - Johnny Franz, Philips, England (Box 47, Folder 15)
    - Phil ? Music Festival, June 8, 1954; 9 photographs (Box 47, Folder 16)
    - Non-matted B&W, TOURING, 112 photographs (Box 47, Folder 17)
    - Andy Williams, 4 photographs (Box 47, Folder 18)
    - Non-matted B&W, TOURING, 41 photographs (Box 47, Folder 19)
    - Erroll Garner & Pope, 42 photographs (Box 47, Folder 20)
    - Autographed Photos, 9 photographs (Box 47, Folder 21)
      Photographs autographed by assorted celebrities, given as gifts to Erroll Garner and Martha Glaser.
    - B&W Touring, 244 photographs (Box 47, Folder 22-23)
    - Erroll Garner with Ralph Gleason, 2 photographs (Box 47, Folder 24)
    - Martha [Glaser] & Erroll [Garner], 91 photographs (Box 47, Folder 25-26)
      Assorted photographs of Erroll Garner with his longtime manager and close friend, Martha Glaser.
    - Susan Rosenberg & Erroll [Garner], 2 items (Box 47, Folder 27)
      Photographs of Erroll Garner with Martha Glaser's niece, Susan Rosenberg.
    - Correspondence about photos, 4 items (Box 47, Folder 28)
    - Avedon photo correspondence, 1955; 1 item (Box 47, Folder 29)
    - Erroll Garner and Joe Glaser Agency and Tony Bennett, 3 photographs (Box 47, Folder 30)
    - Autographed photos, 15 photographs (Box 47, Folder 31)
      Includes autographed photographs of Duke Ellington, Pearl Bailey, Arthur Godfrey, Helem Humes, and Erroll Garner.
  - Negatives, Contact sheets, Color slides, 7.
    - Negatives
      - Black & White Negatives, 60 photographs (Box 48, Folder 1)
      - Black & White Negatives, 64 photographs (Box 48, Folder 2)
      - Black & White Negatives, 109 photographs (Box 48, Folder 3)
      - Black & White Negatives, 22 items (Box 48, Folder 4)
      - Black & White Negatives, 121 photographs (Box 48, Folder 5)
      - Garner; England, 1966; 3 photographs (Box 48, Folder 5A)
      - Master + Negative, [Erroll] Garner Headshot, 1 photograph (Box 48, Folder 5B)
      - Negatives, 3 photographs (Box 48, Folder 5C)
      - Charles Stewart, 7 photographs (Box 48, Folder 6)
      - Gavin Davies, 1 photograph (Box 48, Folder 7)
      - Ken Whitmore, 15 photographs (Box 48, Folder 8)
      - Ted Williams, 120 photographs (Box 48, Folder 9)
      - Vernon L. Smith, 83 photographs (Box 48, Folder 10)
      - Popsie, 2 photographs (Box 48, Folder 11)
      - "Bruno of Hollywood, NYC", 9 photographs (Box 48, Folder 12)
      - Tiny Grimes, 1 photograph (Box 48, Folder 13)
      - JJK Copy-Art Photographers (NYC), 1 photograph (Box 48, Folder 14)
      - Garner w/ Haze Kleveland (Norwegian recording star), 1 photograph (Box 48, Folder 15)
      - Garner w/ George Avakian (Bengt H. Malmquist), 1 photograph (Box 48, Folder 16)
      - Garner, Switzerland, 1966; 3 photographs (Box 48, Folder 17)
      - Celebrities, 108 photographs (Box 48, Folder 18)
      - Miscellaneous, 38 photographs (Box 48, Folder 19)
      - Artwork, 14 photographs (Box 48, Folder 20)
      - Color, 574 photographs (Box 48, Folder 21-27)
    - Color Slides (Sleeved): In Concert, By Photographer, Portraits: Orange w/ tie, Portraits: Piano, Misc., 200 slides (Box 48, Folder 28)
    - Color Slides (Sleeved): Gamma Photo Labs, Vernon L. Smith (Photographer) Portraits: Park (orange shirt), Portraits: Misc, Portraits: City background, 160 slides (Box 48, Folder 29)
    - Color Slides (Sleeved): Miscellaneous Kodak, 46 slides (Box 48, Folder 30)
    - Contact Sheets
      - Black & White, 134 prints (Box 48, Folder 31)
      - Bettye Lane, 1 print (Box 48, Folder 32)
      - Bob Greene, 2 prints (Box 48, Folder 33)
      - Charles Stewart, 12 prints (Box 48, Folder 34)
      - Dennis Stock (Magnum Photos), 10 prints (Box 48, Folder 35)
      - Don Bronstein, 3 prints (Box 48, Folder 36)
      - Herman Leonard, 1 print (Box 48, Folder 37)
      - Lee Balterman, 4 prints (Box 48, Folder 38)
      - Maynard Frank Wolfe, 1 print (Box 48, Folder 39)
      - Ted Williams, 2 prints (Box 48, Folder 40)
      - Vernon L. Smith, 17 prints (Box 48, Folder 41)
      - William James Claxton, 1 print (Box 48, Folder 42)
      - Columbia Records, 14 prints (Box 48, Folder 43)
      - Guild Photographers, 3 prints (Box 48, Folder 44)
      - Photopress, 1 print (Box 48, Folder 45)
      - Sarah Vaughn & Buddy Rich, 1 print (Box 48, Folder 46)
      - Erroll [Garner] & Martha [Glaser], 1 prints (Box 48, Folder 47)
    - Publicity "Negatives", 2 items (Box 48, Folder 48)
  - Matted/Mounted Prints, Color and B&W, 8.
    - Matted/Mounted Prints, Color and B&W (Oversize 49, Folder 1-3)
  - Oversized, Matted and Non-matted by Photographer, 9.
    - James MacArthur, 3 items (Oversize 50, Item 1-3)
    - Aram Avakian, 20 photographs (Oversize 51, Folder 1-4)
    - John Pierre Leloir, 19 photographs (Oversize 51, Folder 5-6)
    - Charles Stewart, 73 photographs (Oversize 52, Folder 1-4)
    - Peter Croydon, 1 photograph (Oversize 53, Folder 1)
    - Lainson Denver (proofs - punched images), 9 items (Oversize 53, Folder 2)
    - Alastair MacDonald, 1 photograph (Oversize 53, Folder 3)
    - Ray Witten, 4 photographs (Oversize 53, Folder 4)
    - T.C. Neil, 2 photographs (Oversize 53, Folder 5)
    - Garner Montage, 4 photographs (Oversize 53, Folder 6)
    - Paul Jones, 1 photograph (Oversize 53, Folder 7)
    - B&W Prints and Poster, 13 items (Oversize 53, Folder 8)
    - Garner at Piano, Review Posters, 4 items (Oversize 53, Folder 9)
    - Erroll Garner X-rays, 15 items (Oversize 53, Folder 10)
  - Non-matted Prints B&W and Color, 10.
    - Color Prints, 11 photographs (Oversize 54, Folder 1)
    - B&W Prints, 35 photographs (Oversize 54, Folder 2-4)
    - Columbia Records Promotional Posters- Mounted, 2 items (Oversize 54, Folder 5)
  - Transparencies and Posters, 11.
    - Damaged poster, 1 item (Oversize 55, Item 1)
    - Album Art, 38 items (Oversize 55, Folder 1)
      Album art for "Dreamstreet," "Close Up in Swing," "That's My Kick," "Amsterdam Concert," "Campus Concert," "One World Concert," Gemini," and "Erroll Garner Plays Gershwin and Kern" in the form of acetates, proofs, and negatives for audiocassette production.
    - Album Art- Erroll Garner, "Close Up in Swing", 5 items (Oversize 55, Folder 2)
    - Album Art- "Up in Erroll's Room", 10 items (Oversize 55, Folder 3)
    - Posters, 9 items (Oversize 55, Folder 4)
    - Liner Notes, "Gemini", 1972; 7 items (Oversize 55, Folder 5)
    - Album Art- "A Night at the Movies", 54 items (Oversize 55, Folder 6)
      Acetates, and film stills for use on "Erroll Garner: A Night at the Movies" album cover and liner notes. Also includes promotional posters for the album.
    - Album Art- "Up in Erroll's Room," "Dreamstreet," "That's My Kick", 26 items (Oversize 55, Folder 7)
      Acetates for album art for "Up in Erroll's Room," "Dreamstreet," "That's My Kick" and a printed proof for "Up in Erroll's Room."
    - Album Art- "Feeling is Believing", 4 items (Oversize 55, Folder 8)
    - Album Art- "Campus Concert", 3 photographs (Oversize 55, Folder 9)
    - Album Art, 3 items (Oversize 55, Folder 10)
      Mock-ups for unidentified projects on Bristol Board.
    - Album Art- "Gemini," "Thats My Kick, "Erroll Garner Plays Gershwin and Kern", 15 items (Oversize 55, Folder 11)
- Audio/Video Material, VI.
  The Audio/Video Material series contains over 4,100 items comprising Erroll Garner's (with his accompanying musicians) live shows, studio sessions, radio and television performances, and interviews recorded between 1937 and 1977, which accounts for approximately 8,375 "songs" or tracks. The inventory includes:
  1,323 Â¼", Â½", 1" and 2" Master and Safety Analog Audio Tape Reels
  1,981 Audio Cassettes, one file box containing 50 unknown/untitled cassette tapes
  652 Acetate Discs, Mothers, Stampers, Test Pressings and Promo Records
  119 film/video recordings: 2 8mm film reels, 25 16mm film reels, 27 Â¾" Tapes, 2 2" Tapes, 2 Beta SP Tapes, 1 Hi8 Tape, 57 VHS Tapes, and 1 DVD
  13 items of "Gear" (cables, microphones, etc.)
  32 empty album sleeves, cassette cases, and CD cases featuring album art for Garner releases.
  The analog sound recordings are not available for public access since they have been reformatted to digital.
  - Sound Recordings, 1.
    All of the sound recordings have been digitized, and are currently available for onsite listening in the ASC Reading Room at our Thomas Blvd. location.
    - Reel-to-Reel Tapes
      Approximately 1,323 1950's-1970's master, safety and unknown open reel recordings (about three quarters mono and a quarter stereo), recorded on 3-track, 4-track, 8-track, 16-track and 24-track machines, illustrating the advancement in recording technology throughout the years. Duplicate master tapes are usually either safety tapes and/or those tapes with different sound mixes or arrangements that were used to select a final version. Mixes can be found with brass overdubs, different guitar, piano and bass balances, etc. Duplicate 1980's recordings are included that may have been copied for remastered re-issues.
      Most of the original boxes include handwritten dates, locations, relevant numbers, song listings and production notes. Approximately three quarters of the tapes were recorded on Â¼" tape and another fifth or so on Â½", with the remaining group on 1" and 2".